POOJA TAYAL

SUMMARY

Marketing professional with proven experience in planning and coordinating marketing policies and program, such as determining the demand for the products and services offered by a firm and its competitors in order to identify new potential customers. Strong expertise in developing pricing strategies with the goal of maximizing profits.

PROJECTS

Effectiveness of Talent Acquisition

HR RecruiterMay 2018 - Aug 2018

Conducted a survey on Talent Acquisition in order to find demographics influence Talent Acquisition.

CONTACT

$\succ\!\!\!<$	poojaaggarv	val417@gma	il.com

9818423276

Noida

LANGUAGES

D 1	1 1	TT.	1'
Hna	lich	Hin	111
Engl	11311,	11111	uı

English

Hindi

EXPERIENCE

Business Catalyst

Wurfel Kuche Jun 2019 - Present

- Built and maintained relationships with key contacts at potential clients, consulting companies and partners in order to get access to new opportunities.
- Developed negotiating strategies and positions by examining risks and potentials as well as estimating partners' needs and goals.
- Introducing and establishing the brand name among the potential clients and partners.
- Enhanced organization reputation by accepting ownership for accomplishing new and different requests; exploring opportunities to add value to job accomplishments.

Hr Recruiter

Ecosylantech Pvt. Ltd. May 2018 - Jul 2018

65 days Summer Internship at (22nd May, 2018-27th July, 2018) Human Resource Internship – Worked under the HR Manager -End to End Recruitment Cycle, Job posting on portals, Mass Mailing, able to handle recruiting needs, building professional relationship, attracting most qualified employees and matching them to jobs to which they are well suited

EDUCATION

Masters in Business Administration(Human Resource)

National Institute of Tecnology, Kurushetra

Jul 2017 - May 2019

Completed MBA(Human Resource) from NIT, Kurushetra with 8.7 CGPA

MCOM

Maharishi Dayanand University, Rohtak

Jul 2015 - May 2017

Completed MCOM from MDU, Rohtak with 60%.

BCOM(Honours)

Maharishi Dayanand University, Rohtak

Jul 2012 - May 2015

Completed Bcom(Honours) from MDU, Rohtak with 65%

SKILLS

Ease in using Ms Office, Communication skills, Internet Savy, Interpersonal skills

